- 这才叫节奏  - 给力啊
- Sick beat. - Super tight.
看来
So...
你们俩从霹雳舞好哥们发展成
The two of you have gone from breakdancing
耳机都一块用了啊
to sharing ear buds.
真可爱啊
That is so cute.
Q 舞帝说你要敢于分享啊
Q-pop says you gotta dare to share.
对了  说到分享  我最近一直都没看见你了
Yeah. Speaking of sharing, I haven't really seen you much lately.
你想不想放学之后吃点冰激凌呢
Do you want to go grab some fro-yo after school?
哦  求之不得  但是今晚我们要上舞蹈课
Oh, I'd love to, but we have a breaking lesson tonight.
来看看咱们新学的时髦动作
Check out these funky fresh moves.
- 预备 约瑟夫  - 准备好了 小迪
- Ready, Joseph? - So ready, digs.
五  六  七  八
Five, six, seven, eight.
咋样  好啊
What? Yeah!
动一动  哦  哦
Some of this? Oh, oh!
蹲到地板上
And down to the ground.
呃啊
Uh!
拉我起来
Beam me up!
（这句话语出《星际迷航》）
- 咋样  - 酷毙了
- What up? - Fist bump.
亮相吧
Good sesh.